### **Marvin Noel**

Address: Timalan Balsahan, Naic Cavite

**Phone:** +63 9568991805 **Email:** noel.marvin26@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

I am highly motivated to learn and adapt to gain valuable experience and knowledge in this industry. I am committed to enhancing and maximizing my skill set through the opportunities provided by your esteemed company. I aim to contribute effectively to the organization's success by leveraging my skills and continuously improving my capabilities.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

Age : 22 Sex : Male Birthdate : January 26, 2002 Nationality : Filipino

Birthplace : Las Piñas, Parañague Religion : Roman Catholic

Civil Status : Single

## WORK EXPERIENCE

02/2017 - 04/2018

# **Experienced Sales Associate at a micro-retail FMCG store**

Responsibilities:

- Maintained efficient records of stock inventory levels ensuring sufficient weekly product replenishment.
- Served on average 15 customers per day answering inquiries, implementing strategic upsell, and managing payment.

02/2020 - 04/2020

# **Internship, Combase Computer Sales and Services, Rosario Cavite**

Responsibilities:

- Assembling and Disassembling of System Unit
- Installing Software unto the computers
- Customer Service
- Fixing Printers
- Diagnostic Troubleshooting (Problem Solving)

#### **EDUCATION**

2018 - 2020

# **Graduated in Computer System Servicing Amaya School of Home Industries**

2020 - 2024

**Bachelor Degree in Information Technology Cavite State University CCAT - Campus** 

# ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Frontend (Tailwind, DaisyUI, Bootstrap, CSS)
- Backend (Javascript, MYSQL, PHP)
- Communication: Tagalog, EnglishFamiliar to Microsoft Software/s

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

2018 - 2020

Graduated with Honors in Senior High from Amaya School of Home Industries.

### CERTIFICATIONS OF WORKSHOPS/ SEMINARS/WEBINARS/TRAININGS ATTENDED

"Cybersecurity Awareness Program for Students of Cavite in Celebration of the National ICT Month Confirmation" Webinar on Zoom, June 02 2022 – Participation.

"Failing means improving" Webinar on Google Meet, June 08 2022 - Certificate of Participation.

"Let's seek success!" Facebook live through Stream yard, June 09 2022 – Workshop.

#### **REFERENCES**

References available on request.

I hereby certify that the information above is correct to the best of my knowledge.